Go every step of the way.
Honey 2 is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Bille Woodruff.
After a brush with the law, Maria has returned to her gritty Bronx roots to rebuild her life with
nothing but a talent for street dance and a burning ambition to prove herself.
Maria Ramirez, played by Kat Graham.
Brandon, played by Randy Wayne.
Tina, played by Seychelle Gabriel.
Melinda, played by Audrina Patridge.
Lyric, played by Brittany Perry-Russell.
Carla, played by Melissa Molinaro.
Honey 2 is a 2011 American dance film and a sequel to the 2003 film Honey,
directed by Bille Woodruff, who directed the original film.
It stars Kat Graham, Randy Wayne, Seychelle Gabriel and Lonette McKee, reprising her
role as Connie Daniels, the mother of Honey Daniels from the first film.
The film was released to cinemas in United Kingdom on June 10, 2011, and
straight-to-video in the United States on February 21, 2012, on DVD and Blu-ray.
The film was followed by two straight-to-video sequels, Honey 3: Dare
to Dance (2016) and Honey: Rise Up and Dance (2018).
The film explores themes of dance, competition,
sequel, bronx, new york city, dance crew.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.